<story>
<TITLE_TITLENAME>
Untitled! The adventure game
</TITLE_TITLENAME>
<TITLE_WELCOME>
Welcome!! What do you wish to do?
</TITLE_WELCOME>
<TITLE_STARTNEW>
Start new game
</TITLE_STARTNEW>
<TITLE_LOADASAVE>
Load a save
</TITLE_LOADASAVE>
<TITLE_RUNCREDITS>
Run credits
</TITLE_RUNCREDITS>
<TITLE_EXITGAME>
Exit Game
</TITLE_EXITGAME>
<ITEM_HEADACHE_NAME>
Headache
</ITEM_HEADACHE_NAME>
<ITEM_HEADACHE_DESC>
A painfull headache
hindering your thinking
</ITEM_HEADACHE_DESC>
<ITEM_TRANSLATOR_NAME>
Translation device
</ITEM_TRANSLATOR_NAME>
<ITEM_TRANSLATOR_DESC>
An alien device
that translates
both text and speech
</ITEM_TRANSLATOR_DESC>
<ITEM_BROKE_TRANSLATOR_NAME>
Broken device
</ITEM_BROKE_TRANSLATOR_NAME>
<ITEM_BROKE_TRANSLATOR_DESC>
A broken alien device.
The insides circutry seem to be
a mix of electronics
and clockwork analogues
</ITEM_BROKE_TRANSLATOR_DESC>
<ITEM_ASSHOLE_NAME>
Asshole reputation
</ITEM_ASSHOLE_NAME>
<ITEM_ASSHOLE_DESC>
It seems I got
a reputation for
being a bit of an
asshole.
</ITEM_ASSHOLE_DESC>
<ITEM_KEEPSAKE_NAME>
{game.Spouse.name}'s keepsake
</ITEM_KEEPSAKE_NAME>
<ITEM_KEEPSAKE_DESC>
A box that you seem to remember
is very important to
{game.Spouse.name}
</ITEM_KEEPSAKE_DESC>
<ITEM_KEYCODE_NAME>
Human habitat security keycode
</ITEM_KEYCODE_NAME>
<ITEM_KEYCODE_DESC>
0-0-0-0-0
</ITEM_KEYCODE_DESC>
<GAME_PLEASESEL>
Please select
</GAME_PLEASESEL>
<GAME_MAKECHOICE>
Please make a choice
</GAME_MAKECHOICE>
<GAME_MAKECHOICE2>
What do you want to do?
</GAME_MAKECHOICE2>
<APT_NAVTEXT_1>
???
</APT_NAVTEXT_1>
<APT_NAVTEXT_2>
Small apartment
</APT_NAVTEXT_2>
<APT_OPTION_WINDOW>
look out the window
</APT_OPTION_WINDOW>
<APT_OPTION_TABLE>
examine the table
</APT_OPTION_TABLE>
<APT_OPTION_SINK>
examine the sink
</APT_OPTION_SINK>
<APT_OPTION_DOOR>
go to the door
</APT_OPTION_DOOR>
<APT_BED>
You are sitting on the side of the bed
</APT_BED>
<APT_BED_QUEST>
What do you wish to do?
</APT_BED_QUEST>
<APT_DREAM>
Weeeee.. you are flying through the sky!
Below you is a beautiful forest, as green as anything you could ever imagine!
Deep down you know you are dreaming, but you can't quite get yourself to wake up.
suddenly you are in a vintage open cockpit biplane flying over the same lands...
                            **CRASH**

Your eyes shook open! Out the window you see the landscape you pictured in your dream.
It seems so nice, yet something seems off. Everything seems off.
You even struggle to remember your own name... 
What.. was.. what was your name?
</APT_DREAM>
<APT_NAME_EXCUSES>
or maybe it was
no why would.. that be my name.. no it must be
no.. ugh.. why can't I remember my name. Maybe it was
no no no no! That can't be right, so it must be
no, I think that's my best friend's name. wait, I got a best friend?? ugh.. what is my name??
</APT_NAME_EXCUSES>
<APT_NAME_SUBMIT>
This is my name
</APT_NAME_SUBMIT>
<APT_NAME_CONFIRM>
ugh.. Was it {game.PlayerName}?
</APT_NAME_CONFIRM>
<APT_NAME_CONFIRMED>
Yes {game.PlayerName} the.. uhh.. something something title titles..
You are sure you'll remember soon enough. Your head is quite foggy.
You think you might have a headache, but you are not sure.
Looking around you see you are in a small room, an apartment maybe? Maybe a hotel room?
You are sitting on the edge of a large bed. Next to the bed is a small table.
On the table there are some small white spheres, a glass of water and two framed pictures face down
At the head end of the bed there is a window.
Towards the end of the room there is a sink with a mirror.
At the end is a door, probably the exit by the looks of it.
</APT_NAME_CONFIRMED>
<APT_SINK_1>
You walk to the sink.
You see glass shards in the sink.
The mirror is broken.
What little of yourself you can see looks like a mess.
You might want to find a proper bathroom and freshen up a bit.
</APT_SINK_1>
<APT_SINK_2>
The mirror is still broken.
</APT_SINK_2>
<APT_WINDOW_1>
You look through the window into the lush forest landscape.
...
The nature seems oddly calming, yet somehow uncanny
...
...
As you move your head around to look form different angles, you notice a subtle lag.
...
You recognize this now.
It is a hologram.
Probably a cheap class 3 eye-tracking laser-holo, you suddenly realize.
Not that you remember what that is, or what it means.
Only that you had a class 5 back..
...
back home...
..had.. back home...
so this isn't home then...?
</APT_WINDOW_1>
<APT_WINDOW_2>
You enjoy the holographic nature outside the window.
...
...
a holographic deer just walked past.
...
Time to go.
</APT_WINDOW_2>


<APT_GLASS_TAKE_1>
You take the white pills and drink from the glass.
</APT_GLASS_TAKE_1>
<APT_GLASS_TAKE_2>
you drank the rest. The glass is now empty.
</APT_GLASS_TAKE_2>

<APT_GLASS_NOTAKE_1>
You did not take the pills
</APT_GLASS_NOTAKE_1>
<APT_GLASS_NOTAKE_2>
you left the glass alone
</APT_GLASS_NOTAKE_2>

<APT_GLASS_EX_1>
The glass is full, and there are some white pills next to it.
</APT_GLASS_EX_1>
<APT_GLASS_EX_2>
The glass is half empty. Or is it half full?
</APT_GLASS_EX_2>
<APT_GLASS_EX_3>
The glass is empty
</APT_GLASS_EX_3>

<APT_GLASS_FRAG_1>
a full glass of water
</APT_GLASS_FRAG_1>
<APT_GLASS_FRAG_2>
a half full glass of water
</APT_GLASS_FRAG_2>
<APT_GLASS_FRAG_3>
an empty glass
</APT_GLASS_FRAG_3>

<APT_PILLS_FRAG>
, some small white pills
</APT_PILLS_FRAG>

<APT_TABLE>
You look at the nightstand table.
You see {_GLASS}{_PILLS}
and two framed pictures.
One with a cyan frame, one with a golden frame.
</APT_TABLE>
<APT_TABLE_QUEST>
What do you wan to do?
</APT_TABLE_QUEST>
<APT_TABLE_OPTION_GLASS>
Examine the glass
</APT_TABLE_OPTION_GLASS>
<APT_TABLE_OPTION_CYAN>
Examine the cyan framed picture
</APT_TABLE_OPTION_CYAN>
<APT_TABLE_OPTION_GOLD>
Examine the gold framed picture
</APT_TABLE_OPTION_GOLD>
<APT_TABLE_OPTION_BACK>
Back off from the table
</APT_TABLE_OPTION_BACK>
<APT_GLASS_QUEST_1>
Take the pills?
</APT_GLASS_QUEST_1>
<APT_GLASS_QUEST_2>
Drink from the glass?
</APT_GLASS_QUEST_2>
<APT_CYAN_1>
You stare closely at the man in the cyan framed picture.
He looks familiar. Very familiar.
You seem to remember he insisted you did not need some expensive frame for his picture.
You study his features closely.
Suddenly it clicks in your mind.
You recognize him now. You think you remeber his name.
</APT_CYAN_1>
<APT_CYAN_SUBMIT>
That's his name.
</APT_CYAN_SUBMIT>
<APT_CYAN_2>
That's right! It's {game.MaleFam.name} your {game.MaleFam.GenderedRole}!
</APT_CYAN_2>
<APT_CYAN_3>
It is {game.MaleFam.name} your {game.MaleFam.GenderedRole}.
</APT_CYAN_3>
<APT_GOLD_1>
You stare closely at the lady in the gold framed picture.
You study her close, trying to remember who she is.
As you are looking in her eyes when you realize who she is.
You suddenly recall her name!
</APT_GOLD_1>
<APT_GOLD_SUBMIT>
That's her name.
</APT_GOLD_SUBMIT>
<APT_GOLD_2>
{game.FemaleFam.name} was her name! It's {game.FemaleFam.name} your {game.FemaleFam.GenderedRole}! How could you have forgotten?
</APT_GOLD_2>
<APT_GOLD_3>
It is {game.FemaleFam.name} your {game.FemaleFam.GenderedRole}.
</APT_GOLD_3>
<APT_DOOR_1>
You walk towards the door.
Suddenly there is a sharp spike of pain in your head.
When it is over you are back on the bed, panting.
</APT_DOOR_1>
<APT_DOOR_2>
You walk to the door.
Your head is starting to clear up.
You open the door, and walk out.
</APT_DOOR_2>
<BATH_INTRO>
You stand in front of the bathrooms. There are two doors in front of you.
One door with a depiction of a man, one depicting a woman.
</BATH_INTRO>
<BATH_WHATDOOR>
What door do you enter
</BATH_WHATDOOR>
<BATH_CHOICEMENS>
Enter men's room
</BATH_CHOICEMENS>
<BATH_CHOICELADIES>
Enter ladies' room
</BATH_CHOICELADIES>
<BATH_MENS_ENTERING>
You enter the Men's room.
</BATH_MENS_ENTERING>
<BATH_LADIES_ENTERING>
You enter the Ladies' room.
</BATH_LADIES_ENTERING>
<BATH_MENS_LEAVING>
You leave the Men's room.
</BATH_MENS_LEAVING>
<BATH_LADIES_LEAVING>
You leave the Ladies' room.
</BATH_LADIES_LEAVING>
<BATH_MENS_WRONGROOM>
You're not exactly sure why you went into the men's room, and not the ladies' room.
Though you suppose it doesn't really matter. There is nobody here anyways.
</BATH_MENS_WRONGROOM>
<BATH_LADIES_WRONGROOM>
A man going inside the ladies room would normally be seen as quite perverted.
But as it is, the ladies is as vacant of people as the rest of this place.
</BATH_LADIES_WRONGROOM>
<BATH_MENS_DESCRIPTION>
What you see is a line of toilet stalls, a large urinal, a few changing rooms, a locker room,
showers, couple of them private, and a dispenser of hygiene products.

Finding yourself in front of the large array of sinks and mirrors.
Some of the mirrors are broken, but you found one that was relativly intact.
</BATH_MENS_DESCRIPTION>
<BATH_LADIES_DESCRIPTION>
What you see is a line of toilet stalls, a few changing rooms, a looker room, showers, couple of them private
and a hygiene dispenser with various.. products...

Finding yourself in front of the large array of sinks and mirrors.
Some of the mirrors are broken, but you found one that was relativly intact.
</BATH_LADIES_DESCRIPTION>
<BATH_MIRROR_MALE>
You have a look at yourself.
What you see is a rugged man with a stubby beard.
You look about as shitty as you feel, yet it does look familiar.
That's a good thing, right?
</BATH_MIRROR_MALE>
<BATH_MIRROR_FEMALE>
You have a look at yourself.
What you see is a tired looking woman with clear bags under her eyes.
You look about as shitty as you feel, yet it does look familiar.
That's a good thing, right?
</BATH_MIRROR_FEMALE>
<BATH_WASHFACE>
You splash some water on your face. It feels refreshing.
</BATH_WASHFACE>
<BATH_TOILET1>
You locate a nice toilet booth, and sit down on a porcelain throne.
Well, ok, not porcelain, these toilets are made of metal.
You relieve yourself right there and then. You must have held it in for a while without thinking about it.
After a while you decide it is time to get back up
</BATH_TOILET1>
<BATH_TOILET2>
You locate a nice toilet booth, and sit down on a porcelain throne.
Well, ok, not porcelain, these toilets are made of metal.
You sit for a bit, resting. You don't feel the need to 'do' anything.
After a while you decide it is time to get back up
</BATH_TOILET2>
<BATH_URINAL1>
You instinctively unzip and relieve youself down the uninal.
it was quickly done.
But soon you realize you have 'other' needs to relive youself of.
</BATH_URINAL1>
<BATH_URINAL2>
you stand over by the urinal for a bit, but you don't feel any need to use it.
</BATH_URINAL2>
<BATH_URINAL_FEM1>
As you approach the urinal, you wondered how it was like for men to use contraptions like this.
</BATH_URINAL_FEM1>
<BATH_URINAL_FEMQUEST>
Try to piss in it?
</BATH_URINAL_FEMQUEST>
<BATH_URINAL_FEM2>
You awkwardly position yourself,
and partially relieve youself down the urinal.
It was kinda fun.
And you mostly hit the target.
mostly..

Still, having done that, you realize you have 'other' needs to relieve youself of.
</BATH_URINAL_FEM2>
<BATH_URINAL_DUMPQUEST>
Take a dump in the urinal?
</BATH_URINAL_DUMPQUEST>
<BATH_URINAL_FEM_DUMP>
You did the deed in the urinal. you slowly back off, giggling a bit as your inner girl got her wicked wish.
</BATH_URINAL_FEM_DUMP>
<BATH_URINAL_MALE_DUMP>
You did the deed in the urinal. you slowly back off, giggling a bit as your inner child got his very childish wish.
</BATH_URINAL_MALE_DUMP>
<BATH_URINAL_LEAVE>
You left the urinal alone.
</BATH_URINAL_LEAVE>
<BATH_HYGINE_MENS>
You examine the dispenser. You find some soaps, condoms, razor blades. Nothing you really need right now.
</BATH_HYGINE_MENS>
<BATH_HYGINE_LADIES>
You examine the dispenser. You find some soaps, tampons, manual razor blades, a few female condoms. Nothing you really need right now
</BATH_HYGINE_LADIES>
<BATH_SHOWER1>
You enter one of the private show stalls.
You undress, and turn on the shower
You note as all the grime washes off you.
you feel a lot better now.
...
...
you dry up, dress yourself and again, and leave the shower.
</BATH_SHOWER1>
<BATH_SHOWER2>
You go over to the showers. But you already feel clean, so you go back.
</BATH_SHOWER2>
<BATH_LOCKERS1>
You take a walk along the lockers
There was not much more to see.
</BATH_LOCKERS1>
<BATH_LOCKERS2>
You stumble upon a familiar locker. {game.Spouse.name}'s locker.
Your hands move on their own, it seems the locker combination is buried deep in your subconsius.
Inside you find a small box.
It feels important.
You take it with you.
</BATH_LOCKERS2>
<BATH_OPTION_SINK>
Splash water in your face
</BATH_OPTION_SINK>
<BATH_OPTION_TOILET>
Visit a toilet booth
</BATH_OPTION_TOILET>
<BATH_OPTION_URINAL>
Visit the urinal
</BATH_OPTION_URINAL>
<BATH_OPTION_HYGINE>
open the hygine dispenser
</BATH_OPTION_HYGINE>
<BATH_OPTION_SHOWER>
Go the the showers
</BATH_OPTION_SHOWER>
<BATH_OPTION_LOCKERS>
Go to the locker room
</BATH_OPTION_LOCKERS>
<NAV_DESC_TEMPLATE>
- {_WHEEL}
 - {_RINGNAME}
 - {_SECTORNAME}
 - {_LOCAL_NAME}
</NAV_DESC_TEMPLATE>
<WHEEL_C_NAME_1>
Habitat Wheel C
</WHEEL_C_NAME_1>
<WHEEL_C_NAME_2>
Unknown place
</WHEEL_C_NAME_2>
<SECTOR_A_TERM_1>
Sector A
</SECTOR_A_TERM_1>
<SECTOR_A_TERM_2>
Mysterius corridor
</SECTOR_A_TERM_2>
<SECTOR_B_TERM>
Sector B
</SECTOR_B_TERM>
<OUTER_RING_NAME>
Maintenence and disections ring
</OUTER_RING_NAME>
<INNER_RING_NAME>
Stasis and healthcare ring
</INNER_RING_NAME>
<MIDDLE_NAV_DESC_1>
- Unknown place
 - Mysterius corridor
 {1}
</MIDDLE_NAV_DESC_1>
<MIDDLE_NAV_DESC_2>
- Habitat Wheel C
 - Middle ring
 - Sector {0}
 {1}
</MIDDLE_NAV_DESC_2>
<MIDDLE_NAV_DESC_3>
- Habitat Wheel C
 - Human habitat
 - Sector {0}
 {1}
</MIDDLE_NAV_DESC_3>
<PASS_SECTOR_DOORWAY>
You pass through the open door separating the two sectors
</PASS_SECTOR_DOORWAY>
<MIDDLE_NAV_TO_SEC_D>
- Large closed blastdoor
 - To sector D
</MIDDLE_NAV_TO_SEC_D>
<MIDDLE_NAV_TO_BATH>
- Outside a
 - Public bathroom
</MIDDLE_NAV_TO_BATH>
<MIDDLE_NAV_DOOR_2A68>
- A familiar door
</MIDDLE_NAV_DOOR_2A68>
<MIDDLE_NAV_ELE>
- A set of
 - elevators
</MIDDLE_NAV_ELE>
<MIDDLE_NAV_CAFE>
- A Diner
</MIDDLE_NAV_CAFE>
<MIDDLE_NAV_TO_SEC_B>
- Large open doorway
 - To sector B
</MIDDLE_NAV_TO_SEC_B>
<MIDDLE_NAV_TO_SEC_A>
- Large open doorway
 - To sector A
</MIDDLE_NAV_TO_SEC_A>
<MIDDLE_NAV_AUXCOM>
- Auxiliary communications console
</MIDDLE_NAV_AUXCOM>
<MIDDLE_NAV_LADDER>
- Emergency access ladder
</MIDDLE_NAV_LADDER>
<MIDDLE_NAV_TO_SEC_C>
- Large closed blastdoor
 - To sector C
</MIDDLE_NAV_TO_SEC_C>
<ACT_READ_SIGN>
Read sign
</ACT_READ_SIGN>
<ACT_ENTER_ROOM>
Enter room
</ACT_ENTER_ROOM>
<ACT_USE>
Use
</ACT_USE>
<MIDDLE_INTRO_1>
You may still be a bit dizzy, as you could swear the floor bends a bit upwards both ways.
The lights flicker, and you see random trash, maybe forgotten items, strewn around the floor.
On the wall in front of you there is a blue arrow poiting to the left.
Arrow are drawn every few meters apart along the entire wall as far as you can see.
All pointing left.
As you note this, you hear a hiss behind you.
The door behind you closes, turning to face it, you note there is a number-plate on your door.
There is an uneasy silence.
</MIDDLE_INTRO_1>
<MIDDLE_INTRO_2>
You exit out of your room and behold the large corridor stretching as far as you can see in either direction.
</MIDDLE_INTRO_2>
<MIDDLE_INTRO_3>
You close the emergency ladder's hatch.
You are now at the middle level ring.
</MIDDLE_INTRO_3>
<MIDDLE_INTRO_4>
You exit the bathrooms and returned to the corridor.
</MIDDLE_INTRO_4>
<MIDDLE_INTRO_5>
You are standing in the long corridor
</MIDDLE_INTRO_5>
<MIDDLE_CAFE>
You enter the door to the diner.
</MIDDLE_CAFE>
<MIDDLE_READ_ROOM_2A68>
The sign on the door reads
    ______________________
    |   C - 2 SECTOR A   |
    |         068        |
    ‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾
</MIDDLE_READ_ROOM_2A68>
<MIDDLE_ENTER_ROOM_2A68>
You open the door to your apartment and go inside.
</MIDDLE_ENTER_ROOM_2A68>
<MIDDLE_SEC_D_DOOR>
You stare at the large solid door in front of you.
There is a painted engraving on the door, it reads
    _________________________
    |      C - 2 SECTOR D    |
    |      EMERGENCY DOOR    |
    ‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾
There is a small reinforced window on the door, you look through it.
On the other side you see a corridor much like the one you are in
except, the lights are all off, and a number of dead bodies litter the floor.
What happened here?
</MIDDLE_SEC_D_DOOR>
<MIDDLE_SEC_C_DOOR>
You stare at the large solid door in front of you.
There is a painted engraving on the door, it reads
    ____________________________
    |     C - 2 SECTOR C       |
    |      EMERGENCY DOOR      |
    ‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾
There is a small reinforced window on the door, you look through it.
On the other side you see.. nothing. just blackness.
No, that's not quite right. As your eyes get used to the dark,
you see the walls on the other side of the door.
They go on for a bit over a meter, then abruptly ends in uneven bent metal.
And you see some small faint light far back in the darknes, moving.
Stars, you realize. Stars flying upwards. You are staring into space!
</MIDDLE_SEC_C_DOOR>
<CAFE_DARK_1>
You entered the door labeled 'Habitat diner'.
The lights are off. You walk in, fumbling for a lightswitch or something alike.
You see a faint blue light, and walk towards it.

...
...

Suddenly you stumble over something.

...

no.. not something. Someone.
And the someone is not human.
It seems to be the size of a child.
The blue light seems attached to the creature.
You cannot make out much in the dark.
But you can make out some faint shapes in the dark.
You can make out a table
You see a long cylinder, maybe a support column?
There is a large opening, maybe a diner counter, in the back.

-- (This part of the story is not fully written yet, expect parts of this to be barebones)
</CAFE_DARK_1>
<CAFE_INTRO_LIT>
You enter the diner. It is still a real mess.
But at least the lights are still on.
</CAFE_INTRO_LIT>
<CAFE_DARK_QUEST>
What will you do?
</CAFE_DARK_QUEST>
<CAFE_DARK_OPTION_1>
Search the alien body
</CAFE_DARK_OPTION_1>
<CAFE_DARK_OPTION_2>
Fumble over to the cylindrical shape
</CAFE_DARK_OPTION_2>
<CAFE_DARK_OPTION_3>
Fumble over to the nearby table
</CAFE_DARK_OPTION_3>
<CAFE_DARK_OPTION_4>
Fumble over to the counter
</CAFE_DARK_OPTION_4>
<CAFE_DARK_OPTION_EXIT>
Fumble out the exit
</CAFE_DARK_OPTION_EXIT>
<CAFE_LIT_OPTION_1>
Search the alien body
</CAFE_LIT_OPTION_1>
<CAFE_LIT_OPTION_2>
Examine the lamp
</CAFE_LIT_OPTION_2>
<CAFE_LIT_OPTION_3>
Search the table
</CAFE_LIT_OPTION_3>
<CAFE_LIT_OPTION_4>
Search the diner counter
</CAFE_LIT_OPTION_4>
<CAFE_LIT_OPTION_5>
Search the mysterius rack
</CAFE_LIT_OPTION_5>
<CAFE_LIT_OPTION_EXIT>
Exit the diner
</CAFE_LIT_OPTION_EXIT>
<CAFE_DARK_BODY>
You fumble around the still cold body on the floor.
It is clearly not human, based on the general shape you can feel it has.
You look for where that faint light come from. You make out some kind of small box.

It is held in some tini small appendeges, almost like fingers.
You can't make out what the box is, so you leave it where you found it.

You can't make out much more about the not-human body.
</CAFE_DARK_BODY>
<CAFE_DARK_LAMP>
The faint cylindrical outline looks at first to be a support pillar of sorts.
But as you fumble closer to it, you touch it.
The texture is smooth and it feels a bit warm.
Feeling around on it you find something that feels like a button.
You accidentally press it. Suddenly a flash of light blind you.
As you recover, you find the room suddenly lit.

You walk back to where the blue light was, the light now invisible compared to the bright support pillar lamp.
</CAFE_DARK_LAMP>
<CAFE_DARK_TABLE>
You funble a few steps in the darkness to the nearby table.

There is something wet on the table. Someone must have spilled something.
You find a plate, on it you found a fork stuck in something.
You accidentally tipped a glass or cup, luckily it seems it was empty.
You can't make out anything that seems important, so you make your back back to the faint light.
</CAFE_DARK_TABLE>
<CAFE_DARK_COUNTER>
You funble around and found what appers to be the serving table. 
In fact you are pretty sure it is a serving table, as your hand landed in a bowl containing something wet and mushy.
It's stew. You hand is now covered in some cold old stew.

Finding some paper towels, or at lest you hope it's paper towels,
as you can't tell in the dark, you clean the stew off your hand.
You find some serving plates, cups, cutlery. Nothing to make light though.
You fumble back to the faint blue light.
</CAFE_DARK_COUNTER>
<CAFE_DARK_EXIT>
You fumble though the darkness out the exit with little difficulty.
</CAFE_DARK_EXIT>
<CAFE_TRANS_RACK>
You walk over to the rack at the far wall of the diner.
It is full of tablets. You take one, and examine it.
There is something written on it, in english.
"Point this end towards you, aim the other side towards who or what you wish to translate. This device is calibrated for the top 5 terran langauges and the 3 prime dialects of Ziruup"
Clearly this is a translation device. 
You decide to keep one with you.
</CAFE_TRANS_RACK>
<CAFE_LIT_BODY>
You examine the alien creature.
It lays leanig, almost sitting, against the wall.
It seems short right now, but looking at the tose, it looks as it could stretch and fold like an accordion.
The creature has six limbs that look almost like tentacles, but with more tentacles branching out in the ends of them.
You find a small box or maybe a tablet in the "hand" of one of those limbs.

You pick up the thing and examine it.

As you do so, you hear a sudden cackle from it. As you life it further up, the cackle stops.
Moving it around, you find the sound stongest near a disk-shaped appendege.
Moving it closer, you suddenly hear a voice.

 - so dark. It is dark.(uintellible cackling noice) Was there an alarm? What is an alarm? (noise) Why is it dark? what... why..
 - so dark. So very hungry. So very very (more noise) extreme. Extreme soemthing. (more noise)  hurt? Pain?
 - pain. pain. pain. pain. dark. pain dark. dark. dark. pain.

The voice stops up more, only occatioanlly repeating the words "dark" and "pain".

Not knowing what you can do to help the poor thing, you leave it to rest in peace.

examining the small tablet you notice a part of it is broken. The front panel, you suppose.
You find some text written on it "point this end towards.." the rest it cut off where the panel is broken.
The exposed insides seems to be void of electronics.
All you see are moving gears, tini shafts, and other tini mechanical clockwork parts.
Some small metal spikes are moving in and out of where the panal would be.

You decide to keep the broken device for now, at least untill you find an intact one.
</CAFE_LIT_BODY>
<CAFE_LIT_LAMP>
The tall lit support beam is still standing, and still lighting up the room.
Looking at it closely, you suspect it might not really support anything. It could just be decorative.
Not wanting to turn it off, you leave it be.
</CAFE_LIT_LAMP>
<CAFE_LIT_TABLE>
The nearby table you saw is part of a dining booth, and is...
it is full of blood!
</CAFE_LIT_TABLE>
<CAFE_LIT_COUNTER>
The serving counter is a real mess, plates, food and bowls are scattered all over the place.
There is nothing worth taking. You return back to the dead alien.
</CAFE_LIT_COUNTER>
<CAFE_LIT_EXIT>
You exit out of the diner.
</CAFE_LIT_EXIT>
<MIDDLE_NAME_LADDER>
WHEEL C RING 2
</MIDDLE_NAME_LADDER>
<INNER_NAME_LADDER>
WHEEL C RING 1
</INNER_NAME_LADDER>
<OUTER_NAME_LADDER>
WHEEL C RING 3
</OUTER_NAME_LADDER>
<LADDER_ACCESS_INTRO_1>
The corridor gives way to a large column, splitting the corridor to go around it on both sides.
On two sides of the column you find large hatches with a colored engraving
        |‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾|
        |    EMERGENCY ESCAPE   |
        |     {_PLACENAME}    |
        |                       |
        |      BREAK GLASS      |
        |          AND          |
        |       PULL LEVER      |
        |        TO OPEN        |
        |_______________________|

You locate the panel as indicated on the engraving.

{_INTROPART}
</LADDER_ACCESS_INTRO_1>
<LADDER_ACCESS_INTRO_2>
The glass is already broken.
</LADDER_ACCESS_INTRO_2>
<LADDER_ACCESS_INTRO_3>
The glass look thin and you feel an odd temptation to smash it.
Written on the glass is a warning.
    FOR EMERGENCIES ONLY!
    SECURITY WILL BE ALERTED TO MISUSE!
</LADDER_ACCESS_INTRO_3>
<LADDER_ACCESS_ENTERQUEST_1>
Smash the glass?
</LADDER_ACCESS_ENTERQUEST_1>
<LADDER_ACCESS_ENTERQUEST_2>
Pull the lever?
</LADDER_ACCESS_ENTERQUEST_2>
<LADDER_ACCESS_ENTER_1>
You reach in the panel, and pull the lever.
The hatch opens and you go inside.
</LADDER_ACCESS_ENTER_1>
<LADDER_ACCESS_ENTER_2>
You smash the glass, and pull the lever.
The hatch opens and you go inside.
</LADDER_ACCESS_ENTER_2>
<AUXCOM_INTRO>
You find a large panel with a screen on wall next to you.
It has the following text painted and engraved under it
        |‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾|
        |   AUXILIARY COMS      |
        |                       |
        | FOR AUTHORIZED USE    |
        |          ONLY         |
        |_______________________|
Under that you find a smaller panel that seem to invite you to push it.
</AUXCOM_INTRO>
<AUXCOM_LEAVE_1>
You leave the auxiliary communications panel alone
</AUXCOM_LEAVE_1>
<AUXCOM_LEAVE_2>
You decide it is not worth bothering with, close the lower panel, and turn to leave.
</AUXCOM_LEAVE_2>
<AUXCOM_OPENQUEST_1>
Push the lower panel?
</AUXCOM_OPENQUEST_1>
<AUXCOM_OPENQUEST_2>
open the panel?
</AUXCOM_OPENQUEST_2>
<AUXCOM_STATUS_1>
You push the panel. The panel lowers as a latch to reveal a keyboard.
The screen turns on and displays the text
        ' AUXILLARY COMS ONLINE. DO YOU WISH TO PLACE A CALL?'
</AUXCOM_STATUS_1>
<AUXCOM_STATUS_2>
You push the panel.  The panel lowers as a latch to reveal a keyboard.
The screen remains off for a while. Then you hear a beep.
</AUXCOM_STATUS_2>
<AUXCOM_STATUS_3>
The screen turns on and displays the text
        'CONNECTION RE-ESTABLISHED! DO YOU WISH TO PLACE A CALL?'
</AUXCOM_STATUS_3>
<AUXCOM_STATUS_4>
You push the panel. The panel lowers as a latch to reveal a keyboard.
</AUXCOM_STATUS_4>
<AUXCOM_STATUS_5>
The screen turns on, but displays static.
Unseen speakers make some sort of repeated beeping pattern that
seems oddly familiar, but you cannot quite place it.

You notice a handle on the side of the panel the screen is on.
</AUXCOM_STATUS_5>
<AUXCOM_STATUS_6>
Opening the panel you find a mess of vires, some of them lose.
Unfortunetly, none of them are labled, and all have the same port shape.
The only diffrence is the thinkness and color of the cables.

You take a moment to brainstorm ideas on what do with with the cables.
...
..
.
You made a list of things you could try.
</AUXCOM_STATUS_6>
<AUXCOM_WIREOPTION_1>
Disconnect thick black cable and plug it into white socket
</AUXCOM_WIREOPTION_1>
<AUXCOM_WIREOPTION_2>
Plug blue cable into blue socket
</AUXCOM_WIREOPTION_2>
<AUXCOM_WIREOPTION_3>
disconnect red/white striped cable and plug it in white socket
</AUXCOM_WIREOPTION_3>
<AUXCOM_WIREOPTION_4>
disconnect red/white striped cable and plug it in blue socket
</AUXCOM_WIREOPTION_4>
<AUXCOM_WIREOPTION_5>
Disconnect thick Blue cable and plug it into white socket
</AUXCOM_WIREOPTION_5>
<AUXCOM_WIREOPTION_6>
disconnect thick black cable and taste it.
</AUXCOM_WIREOPTION_6>
<AUXCOM_WIREOPTION_7>
plug yellow cable into black socket
</AUXCOM_WIREOPTION_7>
<AUXCOM_WIREOPTION_8>
taste yellow cable
</AUXCOM_WIREOPTION_8>
<AUXCOM_WIREOPTION_9>
close panel
</AUXCOM_WIREOPTION_9>
<AUXCOM_WIREOPTION_CHOOSE>
What will you try next?
</AUXCOM_WIREOPTION_CHOOSE>
<AUXCOM_WIREACTION_1A>
You disconnect the think black cable, and plug it into the white socket.
</AUXCOM_WIREACTION_1A>
<AUXCOM_WIREACTION_1B>
At first, this seems to work, as the system seemed to turn back to life. Alas it were not to last.
</AUXCOM_WIREACTION_1B>
<AUXCOM_WIREACTION_1C>
Suddenly there was some sparks in the area aroud the white socket.
You hear a faint hum.
Then hum then turns into a screeching sound that increase in frequency and volume.
Then a speaker explodes, and the system goes black.
You quickly disconnect the black cable, and put it back to where it was.
You decide not to try that again.
</AUXCOM_WIREACTION_1C>
<AUXCOM_WIREACTION_2>
You insert the blue cable in the blue socket.
...
*blip*
....
..
Nothing...
Other than a faint blip, nothing happened. You scratch this off the list.
</AUXCOM_WIREACTION_2>
<AUXCOM_WIREACTION_3A>
You plug the red-white striped cable in the white socket.
</AUXCOM_WIREACTION_3A>
<AUXCOM_WIREACTION_3B>
But nothing happened, and the system is still shut down.
</AUXCOM_WIREACTION_3B>
<AUXCOM_WIREACTION_3C>
The beeps stop, and you notice the screen stops playing static.
You check the screen
....
'What th..'
you are about to say when all you saw was a flat blue line.
But then you noticed it made a wave as you talked.
Well, that's very 'useful'
</AUXCOM_WIREACTION_3C>
<AUXCOM_WIREACTION_3D>
You disconnect the red-white striped cable.
That was a blind end.
</AUXCOM_WIREACTION_3D>
<AUXCOM_WIREACTION_4A>
You plug the red-white striped cable in the blue socket.
</AUXCOM_WIREACTION_4A>
<AUXCOM_WIREACTION_4B>
But nothing happened, and the system is still shut down.
</AUXCOM_WIREACTION_4B>
<AUXCOM_WIREACTION_4C>
You hear an extra beep as you plug in the cable, but nothing else.
The screen blinks, but seems to be back to show ing static.
You check the screen, and you notice the screen now shows something behind the static.
....
'What the..'
you say as you notice a number of red white and blue flags burned into the background of the static.
Well, that's.. colorful...
</AUXCOM_WIREACTION_4C>
<AUXCOM_WIREACTION_4D>
You disconnect the red-white striped cable.
That was a blind end.
</AUXCOM_WIREACTION_4D>
<AUXCOM_WIREACTION_5A>
You unplug the thick blue cable, and plug it back in.
</AUXCOM_WIREACTION_5A>
<AUXCOM_WIREACTION_5B>
You plug the thick blue cable in the white slot.
</AUXCOM_WIREACTION_5B>
<AUXCOM_WIREACTION_5C>
But nothing happened. The system is still shut down.
You decide to leave the cable connected.
</AUXCOM_WIREACTION_5C>
<AUXCOM_WIREACTION_5D>
You unplug the thick blue cable, and plug it back in.
The screen blinks with brief static,
but once again displays black screen with the text 
    'ERROR - PLEASE REBOOT'.
</AUXCOM_WIREACTION_5D>
<AUXCOM_WIREACTION_5E>
You plug the thick blue cable in the white slot
You notise the screen suddenly stopped displaying static.
You check the screen, and find it now displays a black background with a text in white
        'ERROR - PLEASE REBOOT'
</AUXCOM_WIREACTION_5E>
<AUXCOM_WIREACTION_6>
You unplug the big thick black cable, and stuck out your tongue to lick it.
You're not sure why you just did that.
As you somehow put the cable in your mouth, the world goes black.

...

Some time later, your limp lifeless body is found floating around.
Amung the many dead bodies, yours stuck out as being the only one
with extreme electrical burns in the face.
When your cause of death were discovered you were post-humerusly given the Darwin Award.
</AUXCOM_WIREACTION_6>
<AUXCOM_WIREACTION_6_GAMEOVER>
You put a live power-cable in your mouth. Yeah, you're dead.
</AUXCOM_WIREACTION_6_GAMEOVER>
<AUXCOM_WIREACTION_7A>
You unplug the cable in the black slot, and plug in the yellow.
Nothing happened, and the system is still shut down.
You decide to undo it, plugging the black cable back in.
</AUXCOM_WIREACTION_7A>
<AUXCOM_WIREACTION_7B>
You unplug the cable in the black slot, and plug in the yellow.
As you plug in the yellow cable, there was a breif spark, then system shuts down.
You decide to undo it, and never try that again, putting the black cable back in.
</AUXCOM_WIREACTION_7B>
<AUXCOM_WIREACTION_8A>
You decide to try and lick the yellow cable again.
...
Yup, still tingley
</AUXCOM_WIREACTION_8A>
<AUXCOM_WIREACTION_8B>
On a whim you decided to lick the end of the yellow cable.
It had kind of a tingely taste to it.
</AUXCOM_WIREACTION_8B>
<AUXCOM_WIREACTION_8C>
As you lick, you notice the system reboot, and a robotic voice comes the the speakers.
"(( CONNECTION RE-ESTABLISHED! DO YOU WISH TO PLACE A CALL? ))"
</AUXCOM_WIREACTION_8C>
<AUXCOM_WIREACTION_8D>
As you lick the cable, the com-system suddenly comes back to life!
Though it is back to just beeps and static
</AUXCOM_WIREACTION_8D>
<AUXCOM_WIREACTION_8E>
The system blinks and reboots.
Nothing seems to have changed though, still just beeps and static.
</AUXCOM_WIREACTION_8E>
<AUXCOM2_INTRO>
A list of communication nodes show up on the screen.
Some of them with an error-message saying they are offline
</AUXCOM2_INTRO>
<AUXCOM2_CONTACTQUEST>
Who do you wish to contact?
</AUXCOM2_CONTACTQUEST>
<AUXCOM2_COMOP_1>
Connect to main bridge com system
</AUXCOM2_COMOP_1>
<AUXCOM2_COMOP_2>
Connect to main engineering
</AUXCOM2_COMOP_2>
<AUXCOM2_COMOP_3>
Connect to radiation shelter One
</AUXCOM2_COMOP_3>
<AUXCOM2_COMOP_4>
Connect to radiation shelter Two
</AUXCOM2_COMOP_4>
<AUXCOM2_COMOP_5>
Connect to radiation shelter Three
</AUXCOM2_COMOP_5>
<AUXCOM2_COMOP_6>
Connect to radiation shetter Four
</AUXCOM2_COMOP_6>
<AUXCOM2_COMOP_7>
Connect to Auxillary coms, wheel One
</AUXCOM2_COMOP_7>
<AUXCOM2_COMOP_8>
Connect to Auxillary coms, wheel two
</AUXCOM2_COMOP_8>
<AUXCOM2_COMOP_9>
Connect to Auxillary coms, wheel four
</AUXCOM2_COMOP_9>
<AUXCOM2_COMOP_CARGO>
Connect to main cargo bay
</AUXCOM2_COMOP_CARGO>
<AUXCOM2_COMOP_EXIT>
Exit the auxillary com system
</AUXCOM2_COMOP_EXIT>
<AUXCOM2_NO_RESP_1>
You attempt to make your connection.
...
....
.....
... ....
... .... .....
ERROR: CONNECTION TIMED OUT, SYSTEM MAY BE OFFLINE!
</AUXCOM2_NO_RESP_1>
<AUXCOM2_RESP_CARGO>
You attempt to make your connection.
...
....
.. '-oming from inside Wheel C!' 'What?! Hello, who's there!?'
You hear two voices from the com system.
</AUXCOM2_RESP_CARGO>
<AUXCOM2_RESP_EXIT>
You close the lower panel, shutting down the system
</AUXCOM2_RESP_EXIT>
<AUXCOM3_INTRO_ASS>
What? You again? uhm.. sorry, just lost connection!
(call disconnected!)
</AUXCOM3_INTRO_ASS>
<AUXCOM3_INTRO_THANKS>
Hey! Good job with the reactor!
The accellerator seems to be running stable for now.
It will not last long, but at least we aren't in a hurry any more.
Looks like we got maybe two hours. Though bestnot wait that long.

Alright, what I need you to do now, is to rescue everyone who is stuck in stasis.
Any questions?
</AUXCOM3_INTRO_THANKS>
<AUXCOM3_INTRO_RETURN>
Hello again.
Again, thanks for fixing the reactor. We still got some time.
Did you have more questions?
</AUXCOM3_INTRO_RETURN>
<AUXCOM3_INTRO_PLZFIX>
Hi?
Look, our systems say the reactor is still in a bad condition!
We don't have time to chat!
Either fix the reactor, or get out of there!
</AUXCOM3_INTRO_PLZFIX>
<AUXCOM_CONTACT_MADE>
The people on the other side of the call is waiting for you to answer.
</AUXCOM_CONTACT_MADE>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_1_QUEST>
What do you say?
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_1_QUEST>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_1_OPTION_1>
I'm {game.PlayerName}. I'm lost, where am I?
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_1_OPTION_1>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_1_OPTION_2>
Help, I don't know who or where I am!
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_1_OPTION_2>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_1_OPTION_3>
uhh
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_1_OPTION_3>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_1_OPTION_4>
I.. I think my name is {game.PlayerName}. I find it hard to remember.
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_1_OPTION_4>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_1A>
Ok. {_P}, I need you to stay calm. I'm gonna get some help
(The woman you were talking leaves)
...
(A man, an engineer by the looks of his attire, takes her place)
Ok, {_P}. I am not gonna lie, you are in a bit of touble. We are gonna do what we can to help you.
We are onboard the Ziruupan reseach vessel Tikrosa-al on route from Sol to Proxima Centauri.
The reason why you are having a hard time to remeber anything, is likly due to the stasis-pod.
Amnesia is a side-effect of the stasis.
Alright, listen up!
The reactor onboard is about to explode, so were about to detach the module when you contacted us.

Look {_P}, I need you to find the emergency ladd..
(the man is rudely interrupted by a third person)
Hey! I know you. You're {game.FemaleFam.name}'s {game.FemaleFam.GenderedRolePlayer} right?
You're a engineer, right? Maybe you could try to stabilize the reactor temporarily?
There are still lots of people stuck in stasis in the upper ring!

Look, {game.PlayerName}, I woulden't blame you for just making a run for the ladder to save yourself, but you could save those people!
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_1A>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2A_QUEST>
How do you respond?
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2A_QUEST>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2A_OPTION_1>
Screw them! I'm out of here! I'm gonna climb down and get out of here!
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2A_OPTION_1>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2A_OPTION_2>
I.. I am not gonna take that chance. I'm just gonna go meet you up the ladder!
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2A_OPTION_2>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2A_OPTION_3>
Alright, how do I get to the reactor?
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2A_OPTION_3>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2A_OPTION_4>
What exacly happened?
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2A_OPTION_4>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2A_SCREWIT>
Well, ehm.. that's rude. ..
uh well, sure go DOWN the ladder. Uh, and take your good time too.
Got to go, bye!

(The call has ended)
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2A_SCREWIT>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2A_NO>
I see. Well, the reactor will reach a meltdown in just a few minutes, we need to detach the module before then.
You need to hurry! The escape ladder should be nearby. You need to climb up as fast as you can.
In case you need to pass though a locked security door, the code is 0-0-0-0-0. And, please dont ask.
Again, the code is 0-0-0-0-0!
We will meet you at the airlock in the module core.
Please beware, you will be weightless up here!
See you soon!

(The call has ended)
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2A_NO>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2A_YES>
Thanks for doing this!
Ok, there won't be much time, but we will hold off detaching the module as long as we can.
First of, you need a translation device. There should be a few in the diner.
Without one, you would have a hard time reading the manuals and displays.
Once you have one, you need to get down to the outer ring.
Do not use the elevators, that system is down. You will need to climb the emergency ladders

You should find the emergency stairs nearby. You need to climb down to the outermost ring.
The nearest reactor-node will not be far from the ladder.
You need to first initalize the emergency cooling system, then the emergency particle decelerator.
In that order! You will find detailed manuals on how to do this in the reactor-node control room.
Doing this will buy us maybe an hour or two before meltdown.
In case you need to pass though a locked security door, the code is 0-0-0-0-0. And, please dont ask.
Again, the code is 0-0-0-0-0!
You need to hurry! Get back and contact us again once you have done it!

(The call has ended)
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2A_YES>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2A_WUT>
There was the revolt down in the outer ring,
the so-called {OUTER_RING_NAME}.
The fighting damaged the reactor-ring.
We don't have time to discuss details.
I need you to either stabilize the reactor so we can save everyone, or get you safely out of there!
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2A_WUT>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_1B_REACTOR_QUEST>
Ok, {_P}, I need you to stay calm. First off I need to know, was it you who stabilized the reactor?
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_1B_REACTOR_QUEST>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_1B_PART_1A>
Well, thanks for that, {_P}. We were starting to sweat bullets up here.
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_1B_PART_1A>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_1B_PART_1B>
No? Well, then there must be more of you awake down there {_P},
you should get in contact with them as soon as possible.
They would likly be down below you in the outer ring
also known as the {OUTER_RING_NAME}.
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_1B_PART_1B>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_1B_PART_2A>
Thanks for fixing the reactor! {game.FemaleFam.name} told me you were good with machines, {game.PlayerName}. I guess this proves it.
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_1B_PART_2A>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_1B_PART_2B>
It was you who fixed the reactor, wasen't it?
{game.FemaleFam.name} warned me you were as good a jokesteer as an engineer, {game.PlayerName}.
Besides, I can tell. Your voice carries some residual effect from someone resently exposed to micro-time loops.
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_1B_PART_2B>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_1B>
{_REACT_1}
Anyways, please hold the line for a bit, I'm gonna get some help.
(The woman you were talking leaves)
...
(A man, an engineer by the looks of his attire, takes her place)
Alright, {_P}, I am not gonna lie. You are in a bit of trouble.
But thanks to the temporary fix to the reactor, we got some time.
First of, since we got the time, let me explain what has happened.

The reason why you are having a hard time to remeber anything, is likly due to the stasis-pod.
Amnesia is a side-effect of the stasis.
Your memories will come back to you slowly over time.
Quite slowly in fact.
Last time it took me a year to even remeber the invasion.
I suppose I should fill you in. Here's the short.

We are onboard the Ziruupan reseach vessel Tikrosa-al on route from Sol to Proxima Centauri.
Some 10 or so years ago now, the Ziruup Empire invaded Earth.
Well, as much as you could call it an invasion.
Their fighterplanes were armed with semi-automatic ballistas.
And their soldiers were armed with primitive spears.
From what we heard from the radio, they called it the "5 hour world war" back home.

Still, they managed to abduct a good number of us from around the world befo..
(the man is rudely interrupted by a third person)

Hey! I know you. You're {game.FemaleFam.name}'s {game.FemaleFam.GenderedRolePlayer} right?
Thanks for fixing the reactor! {game.FemaleFam.name} told me you were good with machines, {game.PlayerName}, I guess this proves it.
{_REACT_2}
We should probobly have you checked out in the infirmery once you get up here.
But for now, we need your help.

About two hundered people were stuck in stasis during the evacuation.
It is up to you. With the reactor temporarally fixed, we got maybe two hours before we need to detach the module.
I need you to climb up to the inner ring, and awake everyone who is still alive in there.
You will need a securitycode to enter the stasis chambers. The code is 0-0-0-0-0.
Yes, really. just 0-0-0-0-0.

Any questions?
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_1B>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2B_QUEST>
How do you respond?
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2B_QUEST>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2B_OPTION_1>
Why can't you save them?
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2B_OPTION_1>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2B_OPTION_2>
Why the simple code?
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2B_OPTION_2>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2B_OPTION_3>
No. I'm on my way
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2B_OPTION_3>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2B_WHY>
There is a problem with the doors up here.
Look, it's complicated. They were designed by aliens after all.
Sufficed to say, we can't go in, but you and anyone you rescue can come out.
I'm not a door technician, I barely understand the problem myself.
Not sure if we got the time for me to properly explain it.
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2B_WHY>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2B_CODE>
Well.. yeah.. we never expected there to ever be some kind of security issue onboard,
and we kinda still don't, so we never bothered to change the factory settings.
Don't worry about it.
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2B_CODE>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2B_EXIT>
Good luck.
(Call disconnected)
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_2B_EXIT>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_3_QUEST>
How do you respond?
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_3_QUEST>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_3_OPTION_CODE>
What was that code again?
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_3_OPTION_CODE>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_3_OPTION_TRUTH>
Exacly what happened?
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_3_OPTION_TRUTH>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_3_OPTION_EXIT>
Not right now. Bye.
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_3_OPTION_EXIT>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_3_CODE>
As we said earlier, the code is 0-0-0-0-0.
Again, please don't mock us for not changing the factory settings.
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_3_CODE>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_3_EXIT>
Ok then. Hope to see you here soon.
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_3_EXIT>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_3_TRUTH>
Ok then. Here are the full story
We are onboard the Ziruupan reseach vessel Tikrosa-al on route from Sol to Proxima Centauri.
Some 10 or so years ago now, the Ziruup Empire invaded Earth.

Well, as much as you could call it an invasion.
Their fighterplanes were armed with semi-automatic ballistas.
And their soldiers were armed with primitive spears.
They landed worldwide en-masse, and started abucting people.
That's how we ended up here.
I seem to remeber you said you were at a tourist spot in America when you were taken.
Anyways, some of us had radios with us when abducted, and from what we heard,
they called it the "5 hour world war" back home.
Clearly spears and ballistas don't do well against tanks and jet-fighters.
...
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_3_TRUTH>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_3_INTERRUPT_QUEST>
Ask for the short story?
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_3_INTERRUPT_QUEST>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_3_SHORT_STORY>
Uh? Ok, I will short it down.
Most of us is kept in stasis chambers between research project.
Ziruupan scientists usually just do social studies of us, so most of us cooperate.
But earlier today, some a more fanatical scientists decided to disect some of us.
This is what led to the riot that damaged the reactor.

IS there anything else you want to know?
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_3_SHORT_STORY>
<AUXCOM_DIALOGE_3_FULL_STORY>
All in all, Ziruup forces abucted 451 people during the retreat.
Along with several tons of precius metals, equiptment, food supplies from places they raided.
They also raided a dump for some reason, so we got a cargo bay filled with all sort of rubbish.

Well, as we left Earth at a speed faster than anything that could be lauched from Earth, we all soon realized we were trapped.
There were an attempt to take control of the vessel, but...
Well, spears and ballistas do well against unarmed people.

After the initial fighting was over, we were forced into this habitat wheel.
Many of us, being familiar with science fiction and alien abduction stories, expected some grusome experiements.
But none of that came to be. The studies the aliens did to us initially were social.
They wanted to understand our langauges, cultures, social structure, physical strength, etc.
It was easy to cooperate.

Since our food supply was limited to what was raided, most of us agreed to enter into stasis.
Well, except the ones who refused to cooperate at all. They were forced into stasis.

Over the years we talked our Zirtuupan captors into letting us upgrade our habitat to make it more livable.
Installing common comfort from what we could from the raided supplies and equiptment.
Soon enough, some of our captors started to see us more as accidental ambassadors.

Some that is. Many still belive we should all be slaves for their emperror.
One of the more fanatical scientists decided to go ahead with a disection project, and defrosted a group of malcontent abductees from stasis.
Her reasoning were that since they diden't want to cooperate, they might as well be used to learn our atanomy.
This did not go well.

Since this was done in secret, there weren't many guards protecting the lab.
And so they broke free, started a revolt many others joined in on.
They, or should I say we. Some of us up here were part of the riot.
Anyways, we started to destroy the laboretories in the outer ring.
We diden't know about the reactor back then.
So the thinking was that the worst that could happen were getting vented into space.

We diden't notice at first, but as the lab blew, it pushed the reactor particle accellerator ring out of allignment.
The alarm started as hole-breaches started appearing all over in sector D on all rings. And then later in sector C.
An Zirtuupan engineer told us what was could happen, and so we started evacuating, or more like panicing.
As we started defrosting people en-masse, the already disorderly evacuation turned into an outright stampede.

Just as we got the last group though of paniced folks though, the doors decided to glitch up.
Then you suddenly contacted us. Good thing you did. We were about to edject the module,
using the internal atmosphere as thurst. You would have been sucked out into space had we done that.

Sorry you got left down there.
But the important thing now is to get you and everyone else stuck in the module out before we blow this thing.

Do you have any more questions?
</AUXCOM_DIALOGE_3_FULL_STORY>
<ELEVATOR_DESC_CORE>
The evevator appears as large cyllinder that smoothly sticks out of the inner sphere of the core.
The walls sloping inwards to give way to the elevator doors. You float your way over to have a closer look.
</ELEVATOR_DESC_CORE>
<ELEVATOR_DESC_CORRIDOR>
The elevators breaks up the corridor, as the corridor splits to around a large round column you learn is the elevator shaft,
the walls around bending outwards giving way for the path around the shaft until they hit flat outer walls.
</ELEVATOR_DESC_CORRIDOR>
<ELEVATOR_DESC>
{_DESC}
You find six elevator doors in pairs of two around the large cylinder.
You also locate a set of call-buttons for {_BUTTONSET}, whatever that last one means.
</ELEVATOR_DESC>
<ELEVATOR_BUTTONSET_CORE>
down and 'cargo'
</ELEVATOR_BUTTONSET_CORE>
<ELEVATOR_BUTTONSET_MID>
up, down and 'cargo'
</ELEVATOR_BUTTONSET_MID>
<ELEVATOR_BUTTONSET_BOTTOM>
up and 'cargo'
</ELEVATOR_BUTTONSET_BOTTOM>
<ELEVATOR_QUEST>
Press a button?
</ELEVATOR_QUEST>
<ELEVATOR_OPTION_UP>
Press UP call button
</ELEVATOR_OPTION_UP>
<ELEVATOR_OPTION_DOWN>
Press DOWN call button
</ELEVATOR_OPTION_DOWN>
<ELEVATOR_OPTION_CARGO>
Press CARGO call button
</ELEVATOR_OPTION_CARGO>
<ELEVATOR_OPTION_EXIT>
Leave the elevators
</ELEVATOR_OPTION_EXIT>
<ELEVATOR_PRESS_DEAD>
You press the button.
...
Nothing happened.
</ELEVATOR_PRESS_DEAD>
<ELEVATOR_PRESS_NORM>
You press the button.
The button flashes.
...
You hear an odd clang
...
One of the elevator doors open in a very slight crack.
Then you hear a fizzeling sound, and everything stops working
</ELEVATOR_PRESS_NORM>
<ELEVATOR_PRESS_CARGO>
You press the button.
The button flashes.
...
You hear an odd clang
...
Two of the elevator doors open in a very slight crack.
Then you hear a fizzeling sound, and everything stops working
</ELEVATOR_PRESS_CARGO>
<ELEVATOR_EXIT>
You left the elevators alone
</ELEVATOR_EXIT>
<LADDER_GO_UP>
You climb upwards, feeling yourself getting a bit lighter
</LADDER_GO_UP>
<LADDER_GO_DOWN>
You climb down, feeling a slight stronger pull downwards
</LADDER_GO_DOWN>
<LADDER_TO_CORE>
The ladder-shaft ends in a roof-hatch, you open it and stare into the huge spherical room above
</LADDER_TO_CORE>
<LADDER_TO_INNER>
You open the hatch for the inner ring
</LADDER_TO_INNER>
<LADDER_TO_MID>
You open the hatch for the middle ring
</LADDER_TO_MID>
<LADDER_TO_OUT>
You open the hatch for the outer ring
</LADDER_TO_OUT>
<LADDER_CORE_QUEST>
Exit to the Core
</LADDER_CORE_QUEST>
<LADDER_INNER_QUEST>
Exit into the inner ring
</LADDER_INNER_QUEST>
<LADDER_MID_QUEST>
Exit into the middle ring
</LADDER_MID_QUEST>
<LADDER_OUT_QUEST>
Exit into the outer ring
</LADDER_OUT_QUEST>
<CORE_INTRO_1>
As you push off from the laddershaft, you fly upwards in the low gravity.
You reach the center, finding yourself entierly weightless.
You take hold on a rotating pole. Soon the pole seemed to stop rotating, and the room started rotating around you.
You see the ladder you came out from now no longer as "down", but as part of the wall.
From your perspective, "up" has become a set of reinforced windows at one end of the sphere.
"Down" has become a large open doorway, with a sign lableing it "airlock".
That being said, had you turned yourself the other way, it would be the other way around.

As the room spins around you, you take note of the clearly labled entry points around you.
</CORE_INTRO_1>
<CORE_INTRO_2>
You float mindlessly around in the huge sphere untill you get a hold on a spinning pole in center.
Soon the pole seemed to stop rotating, and the room started rotating around you.
As the room spins around you, you take note of the clearly labled entry points around you.
</CORE_INTRO_2>
<CORE_OPTION_WINDOW>
Float to the core window
</CORE_OPTION_WINDOW>
<CORE_OPTION_SEC_A>
Float to the section A transport elevator
</CORE_OPTION_SEC_A>
<CORE_OPTION_SEC_B>
Float to the section B emergency ladder
</CORE_OPTION_SEC_B>
<CORE_OPTION_SEC_C>
Float to the section C transport elevator
</CORE_OPTION_SEC_C>
<CORE_OPTION_SEC_D>
Float to the section D emergency ladder
</CORE_OPTION_SEC_D>
<CORE_OPTION_AIRLOCK>
Float to the module airlock
</CORE_OPTION_AIRLOCK>
<CORE_QUEST>
What do you wish to do?
</CORE_QUEST>
<CORE_WINDOW_1>
You climb, or rather push and drag your way to the window at one end of the pole.
The pole connected to a set of handrails, rotating with the wall.
It was a awkward transision, but you are now looking out a solid thick window.
{_WINDOW_PART}
You took some time to enjoy the view.
...
.....
... ...
Some debris hit the solid window.
You figure this was your cue to leave and focus on the imminent threat on hand.
...
As you push and drag your way back, you hear a odd bang.
Then an alarm starts howling.
You look back, and see the shutters close.
You hear more bangs, debris hitting the shutters.
Might be a good idea to get out of there.
</CORE_WINDOW_1>
<CORE_WINDOW_1_PART_A>
Unlike the 'window' in the room you woke up in, this window was at least not holographic.
You could tell by the lack of lag when you moved your head, the large solid sliding shutters on both sides of the window
uh and the fact you are looking out into space, and not an idyllic forest.
</CORE_WINDOW_1_PART_A>
<CORE_WINDOW_1_PART_B>
The window gives you a great view into space, it is quite impressive view.
You take note of the large solid sliding shutters on both sides of the window.
</CORE_WINDOW_1_PART_B>
<CORE_WINDOW_2>
You look back at the window area. The window is closed by the huge metal shutter.
You still hear the occational clang and bang.
You decide not to get closer, just in case.
</CORE_WINDOW_2>
<FLOAT_TO_QUEST>
Float over to it?
</FLOAT_TO_QUEST>
<CORE_TO_ELE_A>
You look at the elevator access rotating around.
A huge A is painted on it.
</CORE_TO_ELE_A>
<CORE_TO_ELE_C>
You look at the elevator access rotating around.
A huge C is painted on it.
</CORE_TO_ELE_C>
<CORE_TO_LADDER_B>
You look over to the ladder access rotating around.
It has a huge B painted on it.
</CORE_TO_LADDER_B>
<CORE_TO_LADDER_D>
You look over to the ladder access rotating around.
It has a huge D painted on it.
</CORE_TO_LADDER_D>
<CORE_ELE_C>
You push off and float to the elevator.
When you got there, you noticed a flashing electoric board flashing a read light
and text in english and in alien script:
BRECH DETECTED! NO ACCESS!
You take off back to the pole.
</CORE_ELE_C>
<CORE_LADDER_D>
You push off and float to the ladder.
When you got there, you noticed a flashing electoric board flashing a read light and the text:
BRECH DETECTED! NO ACCESS!
You took off back to the pole.
</CORE_LADDER_D>
<CORE_AIRLOCK_1>
You look "down" towards the huge door "below".
Taking in the details, you see the pole ending a bit before it, splitting into 4 aches around the doorway.
Like the pole itself, the doorway was fixed, and not rotating with the room.
On a closer look, there is a secund doorway past it, and two more again, with only some small gap of room between them.
The inner-most door are closed, but has some large windows where you can see the area past it, clearly.
</CORE_AIRLOCK_1>
<CORE_AIRLOCK_1_QUEST>
Take off towards the doorway?
</CORE_AIRLOCK_1_QUEST>
<CORE_AIRLOCK_2>
You rotate yourself so the doorway was now "above" you.
You take off, pushing and dragging along the pole untill you reach the doorway.
</CORE_AIRLOCK_2>
<CORE_AIRLOCK_2_QUEST>
enter the doorway?
</CORE_AIRLOCK_2_QUEST>
<CORE_AIRLOCK_3A>
You enter through the first two doorways.
you note the middle section between the doors were diffrent than the other two.
It was shorter and had a seam down the middle.
As you were floating though, you were greeted by someone who suddenly floated into view.
</CORE_AIRLOCK_3A>
<CORE_AIRLOCK_3B>
For whatever reason, you decide to drag yourself back to the pole.
As you turned around, you noticed some people float into view on the, with confused looks.
</CORE_AIRLOCK_3B>
<CARGOBAY_ENDING>
As you appreach the innermost door, you hear a muffled barely audiable voice from the other side.
{_INTRO_PART}

Are you alright there {_P}? The door is a bit broken,
so I need you to hold down that lever there while we open the door

{_REACTION}

{_FOLLOWUP}

{_END}
        END OF CHAPTER 1
</CARGOBAY_ENDING>
<CARGOBAY_INTRO_PART_A>
Hey, you must be {_P}!
</CARGOBAY_INTRO_PART_A>
<CARGOBAY_INTRO_PART_B>
What the? A survivor! Quick, let's open the door and get {_P} inside!
</CARGOBAY_INTRO_PART_B>
<CARGOBAY_REACTION_A>
Well, you saved a few people, {_NUM_PEOPLE_SAVED} by last count, that would otherwise die.
I suppose that's something we can be thankfull for. Sad there are still so many more stuck down there.
</CARGOBAY_REACTION_A>
<CARGOBAY_REACTION_B>
Thank you {_P}. We never expected you to evacuate so many people on your lonesome. Sorry we could not help.
By our last count, we're at {_NUM_PEOPLE_SAVED}, excluding you.
</CARGOBAY_REACTION_B>
<CARGOBAY_REACTION_C>
What happened? You fixed the reactor. Was there something wrong with the stasis chambers? Why haven't you evacuated anyone, {_P}?
</CARGOBAY_REACTION_C>
<CARGOBAY_REACTION_D>
Well, at least we got you out of there in time.
</CARGOBAY_REACTION_D>
<CARGOBAY_FOLLOWUP_A>
Well, proper congratulations will have to wait.
You should join the others in the infirmary.
And we need to detatch the module now! Hurry on now!
</CARGOBAY_FOLLOWUP_A>
<CARGOBAY_FOLLOWUP_B>
Wish we could get more people out of there, but it's too late now.
Without that improvised dead-man switch on the other side there, this door is locked for good.
You best head to the infirmary.
We need to detach the module before it's too late.
</CARGOBAY_FOLLOWUP_B>
<CARGOBAY_ENDING_A>
You push and drag your way following the signs to the infirmary in wheel A section A1
You try not to think about how maybe you could have saved some of the people stuck in stasis.
You excuse it in your mind by saying to yourself that there was nothing you could have done for them.
Though in a way, you know that's a lie.
</CARGOBAY_ENDING_A>
<CARGOBAY_ENDING_B>
You push and drag your way following the signs to the infirmary in wheel A section A1
You try not to think about all the people you left behind, focusing instead on the few you did save
</CARGOBAY_ENDING_B>
<CARGOBAY_ENDING_C>
You join the last group of surviors you saved on the way to the infirmary.
Pushing and dragging your ways to wheel A, you meet a crew-member.
You get told that the wheel A infirmary is full, so you change course to Wheel D.
As if from nowhere, {game.MaleFam.name}, your {game.MaleFam.GenderedRole} pokes you on your shoulder.
Apperently, he was in the last group, and you had not even noticed.
Neither had he. Stasis sickness being what it is.
Passing the computer core on the way, you got reaquiented with your {game.FemaleFam.GenderedRole} {game.FemaleFam.name} too, who pushed out of the room below you and hugged you.
putting both of you in a real awkward spin in the microgravity, untill she got a hold on the railing, stopping you both.
</CARGOBAY_ENDING_C>
<CARGOBAY_ENDING_D>
Hearing that comment, you got an odd feeling. How could you have known there were more people missing?
And that you could have helped them? As you push and drag your way to the infirmary in wheel A,
you conclude there was no way you could have known.
...
It is of little comfort.
</CARGOBAY_ENDING_D>
<INNER_INTRO_1>
You have walked around aimlessly for a bit, you don't know for how long
And oof! You just walked streight into a large closed door.
</INNER_INTRO_1>
<INNER_INTRO_2>
You close the emergency ladder's hatch.
You are now at the inner level ring.
</INNER_INTRO_2>
<INNER_SEC_C_DOOR>
You stare at the large solid door in front of you.
There is a painted engraving on the door, it reads
        _____________________
        |    C1 SECTOR C    |
        |   EMERGENCY DOOR  |
        ‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾
There is a small reinforced window on the door, you look through it.
You see the roof and most of the frame of the corridor ahead go on,
with the occational blink from the roof light.
Most of the corridor is blown open to darkness.
And you see some small faint light far back in the darknes, moving.
Stars, you realize. Stars flying upwards. You are staring into space!
</INNER_SEC_C_DOOR>
<INNER_SEC_D_DOOR>
You stare at the large solid door in front of you.
There is a painted engraving on the door, it reads
        _____________________
        |    C1 SECTOR D    |
        |   EMERGENCY DOOR  |
        ‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾
There is a small reinforced window on the door. There is a faint glow coming from the window.
You look through the window.
On the other side you see a corridor much like the one you are in
except, it is littered by dead people, and remains from broken stasis chambers.
What happened here?
</INNER_SEC_D_DOOR>
<INNER_TUBES_LOCKED>
A panel of the door indicates the chamber is closed down by emergency lockdown.
You would need an override key to open it.
</INNER_TUBES_LOCKED>
<INNER_TUBES_VISITED>
You have already cleared this chamber.
</INNER_TUBES_VISITED>
<INNER_NAV_ELE>
A set of elevators
</INNER_NAV_ELE>
<INNER_NAV_LADDER>
Emergency access ladder
</INNER_NAV_LADDER>
<INNER_NAV_TO_SEC_A>
Large open doorway to sector A
</INNER_NAV_TO_SEC_A>
<INNER_NAV_TO_SEC_B>
Large open doorway to sector B
</INNER_NAV_TO_SEC_B>
<INNER_NAV_TO_SEC_C>
Large closed blastdoor to sector C
</INNER_NAV_TO_SEC_C>
<INNER_NAV_TO_SEC_D>
Large closed blastdoor to sector D
</INNER_NAV_TO_SEC_D>
<AREANAME_INNER-ROOM-A>
Stasis room A
</AREANAME_INNER-ROOM-A>
<AREANAME_INNER-ROOM-B>
Stasis room B
</AREANAME_INNER-ROOM-B>
<AREANAME_INNER-ROOM-C>
Stasis room C
</AREANAME_INNER-ROOM-C>
<AREANAME_INNER-ROOM-D>
Stasis room D
</AREANAME_INNER-ROOM-D>
<AREANAME_INNER-ROOM-E>
Stasis room E
</AREANAME_INNER-ROOM-E>
<AREANAME_INNER-ROOM-F>
Stasis room F
</AREANAME_INNER-ROOM-F>
<AREANAME_INNER-ROOM-G>
Stasis room G
</AREANAME_INNER-ROOM-G>
<AREANAME_INNER-ROOM-H>
Stasis room H
</AREANAME_INNER-ROOM-H>
<AREANAME_INNER-ROOM-I>
Stasis room I
</AREANAME_INNER-ROOM-I>
<AREANAME_INNER-ROOM-J>
Stasis room J
</AREANAME_INNER-ROOM-J>
<AREANAME_INNER-ROOM-K>
Stasis room K
</AREANAME_INNER-ROOM-K>
<AREANAME_INNER-ROOM-L>
Stasis room L
</AREANAME_INNER-ROOM-L>
<INNER_TO_ROOM_QUEST>
Enter stasis room
</INNER_TO_ROOM_QUEST>
<INNER_TUBES_1>
You enter the chamber, checking each of the stasis tubes.
Most of them are empty. But not all.
So many dead people.
Dead..
Empty, empty, dead,
empty, empty..
You were about to give up when one chamber your almost passed as empty had someone inside it.
You activated the emergency defrost, and resuced a small child.
You told the kid to evacuate.
</INNER_TUBES_1>
<INNER_TUBES_2>
You enter the chamber, checking each of the stasis tubes.
Only some of them are empty.
So many people are dead.
You found 17 people alive.
As you retrived them, none of them were in any condition to help you out.
You just told them to evacuate as you hurried on with your business.
</INNER_TUBES_2>
<INNER_TUBES_3>
You enter the chamber, checking each of the statis tubes.
All of them are empty!
Well, that's good news.
</INNER_TUBES_3>
<INNER_TUBES_4>
You enter the chamber, you were about the check the tubes when you stumbed on someone.
A man. He is unconscious, but alive.
You decide to ingore him for now, to check on the stasis tubes.
In this chamber, it seems a number of the people died during the evacuation.
You found 4 people still alive in stasis.
You brought them out. It took a moment, but you them to help the unconscious man to evacuate.
</INNER_TUBES_4>
<INNER_TUBES_5>
You enter the chamber, checking each of the chambers.
What you saw almost mad.. scatch that. it did make you puke.
All of them were dead. All of them.
</INNER_TUBES_5>
<INNER_TUBES_6>
The room is chamber with smoke! You fight your way though taking longer
than normal to check all the tubes.
It seems the automatic system that was supposed to wake this group shut itself down
due to the smoke. This smoke would likly kill anyone coming out of stasis unasisted.
That might have been a mixed blessing, as you found most of the occupants still alive.

You took care to help everyone out of stasis, and on their way out to evacuate.
</INNER_TUBES_6>
<INNER_TUBES_7>
You enter the chamber checking each tube.
A found a uneasy number of dead people.
But 12 people were still alive to be revived from stasis.
</INNER_TUBES_7>
<OUTER_NAV_ELE>
A set of elevators
</OUTER_NAV_ELE>
<OUTER_NAV_LADDER>
Emergency access ladder
</OUTER_NAV_LADDER>
<OUTER_NAV_TO_SEC_A>
Large open doorway to sector A
</OUTER_NAV_TO_SEC_A>
<OUTER_NAV_TO_SEC_B>
Large open doorway to sector B
</OUTER_NAV_TO_SEC_B>
<OUTER_NAV_TO_SEC_C>
Large closed blastdoor to sector C
</OUTER_NAV_TO_SEC_C>
<AREANAME_TO-SEC-D>
Large closed blastdoor to sector D
</AREANAME_TO-SEC-D>
<OUTER_NAV_TO_NODE>
Reactor-ring access node
</OUTER_NAV_TO_NODE>
<OUTER_INTRO_1>
You have walked around aimlessly for a bit, you don't know for how long
And oof! You just walked streight into a large closed door.
</OUTER_INTRO_1>
<OUTER_INTRO_2>
You close the emergency ladder's hatch.
You are now at the outer level ring.
</OUTER_INTRO_2>
<OUTER_SEC_D_DOOR>
You stare at the large solid door in front of you.
There is a painted engraving on the door, it reads
        _____________________
        |    C3 SECTOR D    |
        |   EMERGENCY DOOR  |
        ‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾
There is a small reinforced window on the door. There is a faint glow coming from the window.
You look through the window.
On the other side you see a corridor much like the one you are in
except, its on fire!
What happened here?
</OUTER_SEC_D_DOOR>
<OUTER_SEC_C_DOOR>
You stare at the large solid door in front of you.
There is a painted engraving on the door, it reads
        _____________________
        |    C3 SECTOR C    |
        |   EMERGENCY DOOR  |
        ‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾‾
There is a small reinforced window on the door, you look through it.
On the other side you see.. nothing. just blackness.
No, that's not quite right. As your eyes get used to the dark,
you see the walls on the other side of the door.
They go on for a bit over a meter, then abruptly ends in uneven bent metal.
After that, aside from what looks to be some solid tick tube, there is nothing but darkness.
darkness and... lights. moving lights.
Stars, you realize. Stars flying upwards. You are staring into space!
</OUTER_SEC_C_DOOR>
<REACTORNODE_1A>
The door in front of you are full of danger-looking signs.
You activate the translator, and read the signs as
* Reactor-ring control node
* WARNING! radiation hazard
* WARNING! chemical hazard
* WARNING! tachyon hazard.
</REACTORNODE_1A>
<REACTORNODE_1B>
The door in front of you are full of danger-looking signs.
All the signs are in some alien language. You can't read them.
</REACTORNODE_1B>
<REACTORNODE_1C>
You peek inside.
You catch a brief glimse of yourself operating the control system.
The reactor may not be entierly stable, but you have done what you could.
You closed the door so not to disturb yourself.
</REACTORNODE_1C>
<REACTORNODE_1_QUEST>
Are you sure you want to go inside?
</REACTORNODE_1_QUEST>
<REACTORNODE_2>
Alarms bleeping, lights flashing, plasma leaking, then unleaking, as small pockets of local spacetime loops.
As you enter the room you instinctivly step aside to let a oddly familiar {_P1} out of the room.
Suprisingly, {_P4} looked oddly familiar. Looking up from {_P3} hands and at you, the {_P1} looks as shocked as you.
But as suddenly as {_P3} appeared, the {_P1} suddenly dissappeard.

What was {_P4}? A ghost?

You sit down on the chair in front of the controls.
You look around at all the virtual knobs and dials on the control-screen.

Looking to your left, you find a manua.. wait.
..
it's gone.
no, now it's there again.
..and it's gone!
</REACTORNODE_2>
<REACTORNODE_3_OPTION_1>
Try to snatch the manual next time it appears
</REACTORNODE_3_OPTION_1>
<REACTORNODE_3_OPTION_2>
Randomly enter data into the controls
</REACTORNODE_3_OPTION_2>
<REACTORNODE_3_OPTION_3>
Get out of there
</REACTORNODE_3_OPTION_3>
<REACTORNODE_3_QUEST>
What will you do?
</REACTORNODE_3_QUEST>
<REACTORNODE_3A>
You hover your hand over where the manual were a secund ago.
...
There it is! you snatch it!
..!
Ouch!
You got the manual book in your hand, but your fingers are now covered in a layor of some oily substance.
And they feel cold, really cold and numb.
Looking at the where you picked up the manual, it suddenly flashed in again, despite also being in your hand.
Moreover, there was now something else.. your fingers!
your disenbodied fingers appearing out of nowhere to grab the manual,
only to dissappear, and reappear.
You decide to ignore this odd phenomenon, as you focus on your task.
</REACTORNODE_3A>
<REACTORNODE_TIMELOOP_GAMEOVER>
You got yourself trapped in a timeloop, forever
</REACTORNODE_TIMELOOP_GAMEOVER>
<REACTORNODE_3B>
Not knowing what to do, you start hammering on the controls.
You tried adjesting that sqiggly thing, you tried to increase that number, you tried to stop that ticking..
you tried any little thing you could think of..
then you, without knowing what to do, start hammering on the controls.
you tried adjusting that sq..

you realized you were now doing what you did a minute ago. are you stu..
tried adjusting that little sqiggly..

uh no, you realize, as you got your thinking stright again.
you try to undo what you did when.. you try adjusting that sqiggly thi..

'shit' you managed to think as you suddenly find yourself trying to adjust that squigg..
and again.. at shorter and shorter intervals.

The after looping for what seemed like forever, with the intervals going shorter and shorter, they suddenly stopped getting shorter.
From what you could tell, with the little self awareness you could muster, the intervals were at about 1 secund.
And you soon realied why.

Aside from your little looping bobble, everything was gone.
You aren't dead. Not really. But by now, you wish you were.
</REACTORNODE_3B>
<REACTORNODE_ESCAPE_GAMEOVER>
Your got torn in half by an unstable time-bubble
</REACTORNODE_ESCAPE_GAMEOVER>
<REACTORNODE_ESCAPE>
Coming to realize what you are doing is dangerous, you step away from the console.
You reach for the door when you feel a tingeling sensation on your hand.
You move your arm so you can look at it. you brifly see though it.
Then the door opens, and a familiar-looking {_P1} walks in.
The {_P1} looks suprised at seeing you, and steps aside to let you though.
Realizing who {_P4} is, you tried to shout out a warning,
but stopped as you felt a sharp pain in your lower torso.

No, not just pain, absense, you realize, as you suddenly fall to the floor.
The last thing you see before you black out, is yourself working on the console.
</REACTORNODE_ESCAPE>
<REACTORNODE_4A>
You scanned the manual with your translator.
The hand-written alien script of the manual comes out as plain english.
Browsing the manual you find instructions for a number of emergency procedures.
You fully understand every translated instruction perfectly.
</REACTORNODE_4A>
<REACTORNODE_4B>
You browse the manual for instructions.
You find what looks like a set of instructions for emergencies.
Or that's what it looks like.
Without anything to translate the alien script, you cannot know for sure.
</REACTORNODE_4B>
<REACTORNODE_5_QUEST>
What procedure will you attept?
</REACTORNODE_5_QUEST>
<REACTORNODE_5A_OPTION_LIST>
Initiate Emergency cooling system
Engage emergency particle decelerator
Engage emergency particle accelerator
Engage accellerator fire suppression system
Engage control room fire suppression system
Run automatic diagnostics
Engage emergency overload
Shutdown tacheon emitter array
Get out of there
</REACTORNODE_5A_OPTION_LIST>
<REACTORNODE_5B_OPTION_LIST>
Start black squere procedure
Start white line to black squere procedure
Start white line to black circle procedure
Start sparks on red circle procedure
Start sparks on red triangle procedure
Start white line on blue triangle procedure
Start red line on black circle procedure
Start blue line on black squere on red line procedure
Get out of there
</REACTORNODE_5B_OPTION_LIST>
<REACTORNODE_COOLDOWN_1_A>
You follow the instructions, and soon the emergency cooling brought the temperature down.
some of the alarms stops bleeping, and you notice the previusly looping instruction manual disappeard.
Well, your fingers somewhy still remained there, looping as creepy as before, but now they were reaching for nothing.
</REACTORNODE_COOLDOWN_1_A>
<REACTORNODE_COOLDOWN_2_A>
You attempt to follow the instructions for initiating emergency cooling,
unfortunalty, it seems the fire is making it more or less impossible to initiate the cooling system.
</REACTORNODE_COOLDOWN_2_A>
<REACTORNODE_COOLDOWN_3_A>
As you were about to start following the instructions,
you realized you have already done this. There is no need to do it again.
</REACTORNODE_COOLDOWN_3_A>
<REACTORNODE_COOLDOWN_1_B>
{REACTORNODE_CLUELESS}
You notice a dial going down in one direction. some of the alarms stops bleeping, and you notice the previusly looping instruction manual disappeard.
Well, your fingers somewhy still remained there, looping as creepy as before, but now they were reaching for nothing.
</REACTORNODE_COOLDOWN_1_B>
<REACTORNODE_COOLDOWN_2_B>
{REACTORNODE_CLUELESS}
But nothing happend.
</REACTORNODE_COOLDOWN_2_B>
<REACTORNODE_COOLDOWN_3_B>
{REACTORNODE_CLUELESS}
But nothing happend.
</REACTORNODE_COOLDOWN_3_B>
<REACTORNODE_SLOWDOWN_1_A>
You followed the instructions to decelerate the accellerator.
...
It seems to work, for a while. Then suddenly a new alarm starts bleeping.
Fire. There is a fire in the accellerator now.
</REACTORNODE_SLOWDOWN_1_A>
<REACTORNODE_SLOWDOWN_2_A>
You typed in the final instructions for decellerating the system.
...
You check the readouts, and several alarms stops beeping.
The reactor is no longer critical, but that might change.
</REACTORNODE_SLOWDOWN_2_A>
<REACTORNODE_SLOWDOWN_3_A>
As you were about to start following the instructions,
you realized you have already done this. There is no need to do it again.
</REACTORNODE_SLOWDOWN_3_A>
<REACTORNODE_SLOWDOWN_1_B>
{REACTORNODE_CLUELESS}
You notice a dial start going slowly in one direction.
Then suddenly another dial goes to its end in a blink of a eye,
as a new alarm starts bleeping.
You feel the room starting to heat up.
</REACTORNODE_SLOWDOWN_1_B>
<REACTORNODE_SLOWDOWN_2_B>
{REACTORNODE_CLUELESS}
Suprisingly this seem to have done it.
most of the alarms stops bleeping.
It seems the reactor is stable for now.
</REACTORNODE_SLOWDOWN_2_B>
<REACTORNODE_SLOWDOWN_3_B>
{REACTORNODE_CLUELESS}
But nothing happend.
</REACTORNODE_SLOWDOWN_3_B>
<REACTORNODE_HURRY_A>
The instructions for accellerating the accellerator were quite easy to follow.
you just adjusted that sqiggly thing, increased that varible,
pressed that confirm button, changed that dial, adjusted that sqiggly thing,
increased that varia.. wait.. wha
you adjusted that sqiggly thing, incr..
you just had a sudden feeling of déjà vu, as you again adjusted that sqiggly thing.

uh no, you realize, as you got your thinking stright again.
you try to undo what you did when.. you followed instructions to adjust that sqiggly thi..

'shit' you managed to think as you suddenly find yourself adjusting that squigg..
and again.. at shorter and shorter intervals.

The after looping for what seemed like forever, with the intervals going shorter and shorter, they suddenly stopped getting shorter.
From what you could tell, with the little self awareness you could muster, the intervals were at about 1 secund.
And you soon realied why.

Aside from your little looping bobble, everything was gone.
You aren't dead. Not really. But by now, you wish you were.
</REACTORNODE_HURRY_A>
<REACTORNODE_HURRY_B>
{REACTORNODE_CLUELESS}
you just adjusted that sqiggly thing, increased that varible,
pressed that confirm button, changed that dial, adjusted that sqiggly thing,
increased that varia.. wait.. wha
you adjusted that sqiggly thing, incr..
you just had a sudden feeling of déjà vu, as you again adjusted that sqiggly thing.

uh no, you realize, as you got your thinking stright again.
you try to undo what you did when.. you followed instructions to adjust that sqiggly thi..

'shit' you managed to think as you suddenly find yourself adjusting that squigg..
and again.. at shorter and shorter intervals.

The after looping for what seemed like forever, with the intervals going shorter and shorter, they suddenly stopped getting shorter.
From what you could tell, with the little self awareness you could muster, the intervals were at about 1 secund.
And you soon realied why.

Aside from your little looping bobble, everything was gone.
You aren't dead. Not really. But by now, you wish you were.
</REACTORNODE_HURRY_B>
<REACTORNODE_FIREACC_1_A>
You followed the quite simple instruction,
The fire in the accellerator ring went out.
Unfortunatly this also made the accellerater accellerate back up.
</REACTORNODE_FIREACC_1_A>
<REACTORNODE_FIREACC_2_A>
You followed the quite simple instruction,
Nothing seems to have happened.
</REACTORNODE_FIREACC_2_A>
<REACTORNODE_FIREACC_B>
{REACTORNODE_CLUELESS}
You have no idea what this did,
but a number of dials suddenly goes crazy for a short while.
</REACTORNODE_FIREACC_B>
<REACTORNODE_FIREROOM_A>
You followed the quite simple instruction, and...
the entire room just got sprayed by a dense foam, convering every surface.
yuck.
If there acually was a fire, you are convinved the fire would be gone by now.
But there was no fire. 'Why did I do this?' you think to yourself while trying to get foam out of your hair.
</REACTORNODE_FIREROOM_A>
<REACTORNODE_FIREROOM_B>
{REACTORNODE_CLUELESS}
Suddenly, the entire room got sprayed by a dense foam, convering every surface.
yuck.
If there acually was a fire, you are convinved the fire would be gone by now.
But there was no fire. You sigh while trying to get foam out of your hair.
</REACTORNODE_FIREROOM_B>
<REACTORNODE_INFO_TEMP_1>
SAFE
</REACTORNODE_INFO_TEMP_1>
<REACTORNODE_INFO_TEMP_2>
HIGH!
</REACTORNODE_INFO_TEMP_2>
<REACTORNODE_INFO_TEMP_3>
VERY HIGH!!!
</REACTORNODE_INFO_TEMP_3>
<REACTORNODE_INFO_FIREALERT>
-       ALERT: FIRE DETECTED IN REACTOR SUBSEGMENT {_SEC}{_NUM}
</REACTORNODE_INFO_FIREALERT>
<REACTORNODE_THATSME>
It did not take long for you to realize that the 'operator' is you.
This might explain the anomolies.
You should be extra careful of what you do here.
</REACTORNODE_THATSME>
<REACTORNODE_INFO_A>
You followed the instructions to initiate a diognastic of the reactor.
...
    STATUS: CRITICAL
    TACHEON EMITTERS: ONLINE
    TACHEON FLOW: IRREGULAR
    TEMPERATURE: {_TEMP}
    STRUCTURE INTEGRETY: COMPROMISED!
    TEMPERAL INTEGRETY: COMPROMISED!

{_FIRE_ALERTS}
-       ALERT: UNCONTROLLED TIME LOOP EVENT(S) DETECTED AT SUBSEGMENT A06 - POTENTIAL TACHEON LEAK
-       ALERT: UNCONTROLLED TIME LOOP EVENT(S) DETECTED AT SUBSEGMENT A12 - POTENTIAL TACHEON LEAK
-       ALERT: UNCONTROLLED TIME LOOP EVENT(S) DETECTED AT SUBSEGMENT B04 - POTENTIAL TACHEON LEAK
-       ALERT: UNCONTROLLED TIME LOOP EVENT(S) DETECTED AT SUBSEGMENT B08 - POTENTIAL TACHEON LEAK
-       ALERT: UNCONTROLLED TIME LOOP EVENT(S) DETECTED AT SUBSEGMENT B12 - POTENTIAL TACHEON LEAK
-       ALERT: UNCONTROLLED TIME LOOP EVENT(S) DETECTED AT SUBSEGMENT C01 - POTENTIAL TACHEON LEAK
-       ALERT: UNCONTROLLED TIME LOOP EVENT(S) DETECTED AT SUBSEGMENT C02 - POTENTIAL TACHEON LEAK
-       ALERT: UNCONTROLLED TIME LOOP EVENT(S) DETECTED AT SUBSEGMENT C06 - POTENTIAL TACHEON LEAK
-       ALERT: UNCONTROLLED TIME LOOP EVENT(S) DETECTED AT SUBSEGMENT C09 - POTENTIAL TACHEON LEAK
-       ALERT: UNCONTROLLED TIME LOOP EVENT(S) DETECTED AT SUBSEGMENT C11 - POTENTIAL TACHEON LEAK
-       ALERT: UNCONTROLLED TIME LOOP EVENT(S) DETECTED AT SUBSEGMENT D01 - POTENTIAL TACHEON LEAK
-       ALERT: UNCONTROLLED TIME LOOP EVENT(S) DETECTED AT SUBSEGMENT D02 - POTENTIAL TACHEON LEAK
-       ALERT: UNCONTROLLED TIME LOOP EVENT(S) DETECTED AT SUBSEGMENT D03 - POTENTIAL TACHEON LEAK
-       ALERT: UNCONTROLLED TIME LOOP EVENT(S) DETECTED AT SUBSEGMENT D04 - POTENTIAL TACHEON LEAK
-       ALERT: UNCONTROLLED TIME LOOP EVENT(S) DETECTED AT SUBSEGMENT D07 - POTENTIAL TACHEON LEAK
-       ALERT: UNCONTROLLED TIME LOOP EVENT(S) DETECTED AT SUBSEGMENT D08 - POTENTIAL TACHEON LEAK
-       ALERT: UNCONTROLLED TIME LOOP EVENT(S) DETECTED AT SUBSEGMENT D09 - POTENTIAL TACHEON LEAK

    WARNING: REACTOR BREACH(ES) DETECTED!
    WARNING: MELTDOWN IMMINENT!
    WARNING: OPERATOR DETECTED IN COMPROMIZED SUBSECTION B04! EVACUATION IS ADVICED!
{_THATSME}
</REACTORNODE_INFO_A>
<REACTORNODE_INFO_B>
{REACTORNODE_CLUELESS}
The control system starts displaying a large stream of data.
You have no idea what it says.
</REACTORNODE_INFO_B>
<REACTORNODE_OVERLOAD_GAMEOVER>
You found a way to blow youself up. You are very VERY dead!
</REACTORNODE_OVERLOAD_GAMEOVER>
<REACTORNODE_OVERLOAD_A>
You followed the instructions for initiating an emergency overload.
Right after pressing the confirm key on the screen, you got an odd feeling.
The reactor started humming. Did you just make a huge mis..
...
You never got to finish that thought. You just ceased to exist.
To say you were atomized is not entierly accurate,
but that may be the closest terminology to describe what happened to you.
At least, there were no pain.
</REACTORNODE_OVERLOAD_A>
<REACTORNODE_OVERLOAD_B>
{REACTORNODE_CLUELESS}
Right after pressing the confirm key on the screen, you got an odd feeling.
The reactor started humming. Did you just make a huge mis..
...
You never got to finish that thought. You just ceased to exist.
To say you were atomized is not entierly accurate,
but that may be the closest terminology to describe what happened to you.
At least, there were no pain.
</REACTORNODE_OVERLOAD_B>
<REACTORNODE_SHUTDOWN_A>
You followed the instructions to shut down the the tacheon emitter array.
...
The system register succesful, then not successful shutdown, then both at the same time.
{_GOTINFO}

You are completly baffled at what this. You ended the shutdown process.
You decide to try something else.
</REACTORNODE_SHUTDOWN_A>
<REACTORNODE_SHUTDOWN_INFO>
It took you a moment to see it, but you now realized why this is.
Looking over the diagnatic data you retrived earlier,
you see most of the emitters are stuck in time-loops.
They are running perpetually.
Trying to just shutting them down just won't work.
</REACTORNODE_SHUTDOWN_INFO>
<REACTORNODE_SHUTDOWN_B>
{REACTORNODE_CLUELESS}
It does not look like that did anything.
</REACTORNODE_SHUTDOWN_B>
<REACTORNODE_6>
Leaving the room, you fuss over your hand. You are slowly regaining feeling in it.
Suddenly you notice something.. someone in front of you.
You look up at the stranger.
It took you a bit by surprise, but then you remembered what happened when you first came in.
And as before, the other person suddenly disappeared.
You leave the room content you have done what you could to fix it up.
</REACTORNODE_6>
<LEAVE>
Leave
</LEAVE>
<YES>
Yes
</YES>
<NO>
No
</NO>
<TRUE>
True
</TRUE>
<FALSE>
False
</FALSE>
<HUSBAND>
husband
</HUSBAND>
<BROTHER>
brother
</BROTHER>
<WIFE>
wife
</WIFE>
<SISTER>
sister
</SISTER>
<QWASIT>
Was it?
</QWASIT>
<GENDERED_1_MALE>
mister
</GENDERED_1_MALE>
<GENDERED_1_FEMALE>
miss
</GENDERED_1_FEMALE>
<GENDERED_2_MALE>
man
</GENDERED_2_MALE>
<GENDERED_2_FEMALE>
lady
</GENDERED_2_FEMALE>
<GENDERED_3_MALE>
his
</GENDERED_3_MALE>
<GENDERED_3_FEMALE>
her
</GENDERED_3_FEMALE>
<GENDERED_4_MALE>
he
</GENDERED_4_MALE>
<GENDERED_4_FEMALE>
she
</GENDERED_4_FEMALE>
<ITEM_TRANSLATOR_ICON>
translator.gif
</ITEM_TRANSLATOR_ICON>
<ITEM_KEEPSAKE_ICON>
smallbox.gif
</ITEM_KEEPSAKE_ICON>
<ITEM_HEADACHE_ICON>
headache.gif
</ITEM_HEADACHE_ICON>
<ITEM_ASSHOLE_ICON>
asshole.gif
</ITEM_ASSHOLE_ICON>
<ITEM_BROKE_TRANSLATOR_ICON>
brokentranslator.gif
</ITEM_BROKE_TRANSLATOR_ICON>
<ITEM_KEYCODE_ICON>
note.gif
</ITEM_KEYCODE_ICON>
<AREANAME_BATHROOMS-DOOR>
Public bathrooms
</AREANAME_BATHROOMS-DOOR>
<AREANAME_BATHROOMS-MENS>
Men's bathroom
</AREANAME_BATHROOMS-MENS>
<AREANAME_BATHROOMS-LADIES>
Ladies bathroom
</AREANAME_BATHROOMS-LADIES>
<AREANAME_CAFETERIA>
Habitat diner
</AREANAME_CAFETERIA>
<AREANAME_CORE>
Habitat wheel core
</AREANAME_CORE>
<AREANAME_CORE-WINDOW>
Observation window
</AREANAME_CORE-WINDOW>
<AREANAME_CORE-ELEVATOR_A>
Sector A elevator access
</AREANAME_CORE-ELEVATOR_A>
<AREANAME_CORE-ELEVATOR_C>
Sector C elevator access
</AREANAME_CORE-ELEVATOR_C>
<AREANAME_CORE-LADDER_B>
Sector B emergency ladder access
</AREANAME_CORE-LADDER_B>
<AREANAME_CORE-LADDER_D>
 Sector D emergency ladder access
</AREANAME_CORE-LADDER_D>
<AREANAME_CORE-AIRLOCK>
Habitat wheel module primary airlock
</AREANAME_CORE-AIRLOCK>
<AREANAME_CARGOBAY>
Human supplies section - Tikrosa-al Cargo bay 
</AREANAME_CARGOBAY>
<AREANAME_TO-CORE>
Exit-hatch to habitat wheel core
</AREANAME_TO-CORE>
<AREANAME_TO-INNER>
Exit-hatch to inner ring
</AREANAME_TO-INNER>
<AREANAME_TO-MIDDLE>
Exit-hatch to middle ring
</AREANAME_TO-MIDDLE>
<AREANAME_TO-OUTER>
Exit-hatch to outer ring
</AREANAME_TO-OUTER>
<AREANAME_BATHROOMS-DOOR>
Public bathrooms
</AREANAME_BATHROOMS-DOOR>
<AREANAME_APARTMENT-DOOR>
Living quarters room 2A68
</AREANAME_APARTMENT-DOOR>
<AREANAME_ELEVATOR>
Elevators
</AREANAME_ELEVATOR>
<AREANAME_CAFE-DOOR>
Diner entrace
</AREANAME_CAFE-DOOR>
<AREANAME_TO-SEC-B>
Sector opening to sector B
</AREANAME_TO-SEC-B>
<AREANAME_TO-SEC-A>
Sector opening to sector A
</AREANAME_TO-SEC-A>
<AREANAME_AUXCOM>
Auxillary communications console
</AREANAME_AUXCOM>
<AREANAME_LADDER>
Emergency escape ladder
</AREANAME_LADDER>
<AREANAME_TO-SEC_C>
Closed reinforced door
</AREANAME_TO-SEC_C>
<AREANAME_TO-SEC-D>
Closed reinforced door
</AREANAME_TO-SEC-D>
<AREANAME_APARTMENT>
Your apartment living quarters
</AREANAME_APARTMENT>
<AREANAME_UNKNOWN>
Unknown place
</AREANAME_UNKNOWN>

</story>
